question_data = [
{"question": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "true"},
{"question": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "false"},
{"question": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "true"},
{"question": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "true"},
{"question": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "true"},
{"question": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "false"},
{"question": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "true"},
{"question": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "false"},
{"question": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "true"},
{"question": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "true"},
{"question": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "false"},
{"question": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "true"}
]